In the first case, both probabilities would give the same result,
在第一种情况下 这两个概率的结果相同
regardless of whether the user double clicked or single clicked.
无论用户是双击还是单击
For example, suppose a user loads the page, which generates a page view.
例如 假设一个用户加载了页面 产生一个网页浏览量
Then one minute later, they click twice, half a second apart.
一分钟之后 他们点击了两次 概率为二分之一
Assuming that the time interval is longer than a minute, say five minutes,
假设时间段大于一分钟 比方说五分钟
then the cookie definition and the page view definition of probabilities will
概率的 cookie 定义和网页浏览定义将
both count the single unique click and give a result of one.
计算为两个独立的点击量 得出的结果为 1
The click-through rate, on the other hand,
另一方面 点击率
would be two, since both clicks would be counted separately,
是 2 因为单独计算两次点击量
which is a different answer than if the user had single clicked.
这个与用户点击一次的答案不同
In the second case,
在第二个例子中
only the cookie definition would give the same answer either way.
cookie 定义无论以哪种方式都得出相同的答案
Compare these two timelines.
比较两条时间线
In the first timeline, the user loads the page,
在第一条时间线中 用户加载网页
which generates a pageview, then navigate away.
生成一个网页浏览量 然后浏览
Then, one minute later, they use the back button to return, and
一分钟之后 他们使用返回按钮
it generates another pageview.
生成另一个网页浏览量
And then they click a minute after that.
一分钟之后点击
The second timeline is the same, but in this case, the browser cached the page,
第二条时间线一样 但在这个例子中 浏览器缓存页面
so the second pageview is missing.
因此 第二个网页浏览量丢失
Thus, by looking at your data, all you can really see is that there was
通过查看数据 你真正能看到的所有内容是
a pageview, and then two minutes later, there was a click.
有一个网页浏览量 两分钟之后有一次点击
The cookie probability will calculate one unique click and
在这两个例子中 cookie 概率会计算一次独立的点击和
one user in both cases.
一个用户
The pageview probability will also calculate one unique click, but
网页浏览概率会计算一次独立点击
in the first case there will be two pageviews in the denominator.
在第一个例子中 分母是两次网页浏览量
And in the second, there will only be one, giving a different result.
在第二个例子中 网页浏览量是 1 因此 两个例子的结果不同
Finally, the rate will also calculate a different number of pageviews in
最后 比率还计算出分母的网页浏览量不同
the denominator, two versus one.
2 和 1
Giving a different answer.
因此答案不同
In the last case, if two clicks are recorded instead of one,
在最后一个例子中 如果记录了两次点击量 而非一次
this is the same as double clicking.
与双击相同
So the rate will be affected, and the probabilities will not.
因此 比率会受到影响 而概率不受影响
However, suppose, instead, that a click is completely missed.
但是 假设 一次点击量完全丢失
So, instead of recording one pageview with a click a minute later,
因此 不记录一分钟之后有点击率的网页浏览量
you just record a page view with no click.
只记录没有点击率的网页浏览量
All three definitions will give one in the case where there was a click, and
在只有一次点击率的情况下 所有这三个定义都只有一个结果
zero in the case where there was not.
在没有点击率的情况下 所有这三个定义的结果是 0
So all the definitions will be affected.
因此 所有定义都受到了影响
Perhaps it's not terribly surprising that it's hard to choose a metric that
很难选择一个不受这个问题影响的指标
won't be affected by a problem this drastic.
这可能并不十分令人惊讶